Newsletter Records, circa 1983-1987
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Newsletter Records
circa 1983-1987
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Colonial Waterbird Society
Non-SI Records
1 cu. ft. (1 record storage box)
Accession 90-034
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of an addition to the records of the Colonial Waterbird Society. This material is the files of Dr. William E. Davis as editor of the newsletter.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Davis, William E. (William Edwin), 1936-; Colonial Waterbird Group (U.S.)
Subject
Ornithologists; Professional associations
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Manuscripts
- Box 1
  - Folder 1 Colonial Waterbird Group (CWG) Newsletter Questionnaire (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 2 CWG Financial (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folders 3-7 Miscellaneous (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 8 Mock-Up, Vol. 8, No. 2, May 1984 Newsletter (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 9 CWG (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 10 "To be Xeroxed" (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folders 11-13 Miscellaneous (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 14 1984 CWG Council (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 15 CWG Current (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 16 August 1985 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 17 August 1985 NL (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 18 November 1986 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folders 19-20 Vol. 9, No. 3 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 21 March Newsletter, 1985 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 22 1988 Meeting Agenda (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 23 Miscellaneous (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 24 Vol. 10, No. 2, August 1986 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Folder 25 Peabody Museum, LG Journals (Box 1 of 1)